hello
你好
I'm Emily Chang.
我是艾米丽。
General Keith Alexander is here
亚力山大基思将军
to tackle tech's role
in counter-terrorism,
处理技术的作用
but first, a quick glimpse
with Richard Hendricks,
但首先，快速一瞥
founder and CEO
的创始人和首席执行官
of the hot new compression
platform Pied Piper,
热压缩新
and Erlich Bachman, Chief Visionary.
和艾巴赫曼，首席顾问。
Oh, Emily Chang,
哦，艾米丽，
it is just splendid to be here with you,
和你在一起真是太好了，
at historical Pier Three,
with a breathtaking view
在历史码头三，
of the
Embarcadero Center
的
and the flag of San Francisco.
三藩的旗帜。
Now, Richard...
现在，李察…
Richard actually developed
实际上是李察发展
this technology in my incubator.
这项技术在我的孵化器。
I am listed--
I was originally listed
我列出了--
under the white pages
as "Erlich Blachman,"
在白纸下
uh, with an "L," a typo that
apparently couldn't be changed,
嗯，有一个“L”型，
and then Google indexed it, so
I've been dealing with that.
然后谷歌索引它，所以
Richard, Pied Piper has
taken off like a rocket.
李察，吹笛手了
More than a hundred thousand installs
超过十万安装
in just ten days. Is that right?
在just ten天内是不是？
Uh... uh, yes.
呃…嗯，是的。
Pretty amazing.
很神奇的。
And you have a last-minute invite
你有一个最后的邀请
to the "Vanity Fair"
Summit dinner tonight.
“名利场”
Quite an honor for such a young company.
相当荣幸为这样一个年轻的公司。
Richard, maybe you can
comment on this one?
李察，也许你可以
Yeah, we are the-- finally
the-- the belles of the balls.
是的，我们是最后的
I mean, uh, ball.
我的意思是，呃，球。
Now, some people are calling
you the next unicorn.
现在，有些人在呼唤
Have you guys thought about that?
你们有没有想过？
You could have a billion-dollar company.
你可以有十亿美元的公司。
Erlich, you could own five
percent of a billion dollars.
法国，你可以拥有五
Uh, ten, actually.
嗯，十岁，实际上。
Richard, this is boring.
李察，这很无聊。
- Shit.
- No, no, no.
-该死。
He was--
he was an early investor.
他——
Again, it's... Erlich Bachman.
再次，它的..法国巴赫曼。
If you Google that, it'll say,
"Did you mean Erlich Blachman?"
如果你谷歌，它会说，
You can click on that link,
你可以点击这个链接，
it'll give you the correct
results for Erlich Bachman.
它会给你正确的
Should we take some calls?
我们应该打电话吗？
We don't do that here.
我们不这样做。
I just know what I saw, Richard.
我只知道我看到了什么，李察。
No, come on. Look, she's married,
she just had another baby.
不，来。看，她结婚了，
If you pushed a little harder, you could
have scored right there on camera.
如果你努力的话，你可以
- You should get her phone number.
- Shut up.
•你应该得到她的电话号码。
Oh. This is actually, uh,
Jian-Yang pranking me.
哦.这实际上是，嗯，
I should take it.
我应该接受它。
Yes, of course I have frog's legs.
Why do you ask?
是的，当然我有青蛙的腿。
Are you serious? Have you honestly still
not told him that you sold your shares?
你是认真的吗？你真的仍然
You can't keep lying to him like this.
你不能这样对他撒谎。
It's not technically a lie.
这不是一个技术上的谎言。
My shares don't transfer to Raviga
我的股份不转让raviga
until the next board meeting.
直到下一次董事会会议。
Come on, it's been ten days.
来吧，已经十天了。
I know, I know, but, you
know, the TechCrunch thing
我知道，我知道，但是，你
came up and then there
was the Reddit AMA
出现在那里
and, you know, now this Bloomberg thing.
而且，你知道，现在这个彭博的事情。
And besides, let's be honest, Richard
shouldn't be in the public eye
再说，让我们诚实，李察
without me along to help. Did you see the
skeeved-out look on Emily Chang's face?
没有我一起帮助。你看见了吗
I thought she was going to walk off set.
我以为她要走了。
Erlich, you're lying to him,
艾，你对他说谎，
and you made me a part of it,
so now I'm lying to him, too.
你让我做了一个部分，
The longer you wait, the
worse this is gonna get.
你等待的时间越长，
- All right, fine, I'll tell him.
- When?
好吧，好吧，我会告诉他。
After the "Vanity Fair" thing tonight.
I mean, did you see the guest list?
在“名利场”今晚的事情。
Monica, throw me a bone here.
莫妮卡，丢根骨头给我。
24 hours, then I'm telling him.
24个小时，然后我告诉他。
- Fine, I'll tell him. I'll tell Richard.
- I'm serious.
-好的，我会告诉他。我会告诉李察。
- Tell me what?
- I'm not joking--
告诉我什么？
Um, it was, uh, Jian-Yang.
嗯，这是，嗯，简。
He said to tell you that
Phillip McCrevis left word.
他说要告诉你
Oh, who's "Fill-up My--" Oh.
哦，谁的“补我的-”哦。
♪
Richard, we'd better get our
asses in first fucking gear
李察，我们最好把我们的
if we want to make it to
this "Verge" photoshoot.
如果我们想让它
Oh, shit. That's today?
哦，该死。那是今天吗？
Yes, I assumed that's why you're still
是的，我认为这就是为什么你仍然
- wearing your Bloomberg makeup.
- No.
•戴上你的彭博化妆。
No, I was just--
I kind of like the way it--
不，我只是--
can we just push this
to next week, please?
我们可以推这个
They don't really do that.
他们真的不这样做。
Okay, well, can you go?
好吧，你能去吗？
Please? I just have a ton of work,
请？我只是有一大堆的工作，
and honestly I would be really happy
说实话，我真的很高兴
if I never had to do
any of this ever again
如果我不曾做
and then you were just
the face of the company.
然后你只是
You know what I mean? Oh, shit.
你知道我的意思吗？哦，该死。
What-- what time is this
"Vanity Fair" thing?
什么-什么时候是这个
It's tonight. I figure
we're wheels up by 6:00,
这是今晚。我的身影
then we can check into the hotel,
shit, shave and shit again.
然后我们可以到酒店入住，
- Get a cocktail.
- What hotel?
得到一杯鸡尾酒。
Eavesdropping. Well, if you must know,
窃听。好吧，如果你必须知道，
we got a suite at the Fairmont,
and they're sending a car.
我们在费尔蒙有一套房，
I think Richard deserves it. And
then I figured tomorrow in the a.m.,
我认为李察应该得到它。和
we would sleep in and
have a nice brunch.
我们会睡在
I don't have time for a brunch.
I have to be back here.
我没有一个午餐时间。
Come on, eggs benny, a little spinach
tartar, you'll flirt with the waitress.
来吧，鸡蛋本尼，一点菠菜
Killer. And, uh, we'll have a nice talk.
杀手。嗯，我们有一个很好的谈话。
- Talk? What about?
- You know, things, all sorts of themes.
交谈？是什么样的？
So tomorrow, you, me, brunch
所以明天，你，我，早午餐
and, uh, one word... frittata.
嗯，一个词…煎蛋饼。
Hey, fellas, is it me or is
it a bit chilly in here?
嘿，伙计们，这是我还是
What in God's name is that?
上帝的名字是什么？
What do you think it is? It's a jacket!
你认为它是什么？这是一件夹克！
Now, I only
ordered one as a sample,
现在，我只
but once I have your sizes,
we can all have them.
但一旦我有你的尺寸，
Why would we all want them?
One is already too many.
为什么我们都要他们？
I don't mean in the house. I
mean, like, in the world.
我不是指在房子里。我
Now Gilfoyle, I have you at
about a 40 long? Am I right?
现在你已在吉尔福伊尔，我
If my mother was naked
and dead in the street,
如果我的母亲是裸体的
I would not cover her
body with that jacket.
我不会掩盖她
Gilf.
基尔夫。
Jared, now that you're here,
贾里德，现在你来了，
we need two new tables
in the game room. Yeah?
我们需要新的桌子
Okay. Well, maybe against the doors?
可以.好吧，也许在门上？
Oh, hold on, there's more.
哦，坚持，有更多。
Because 'awesome
world-changing compression company'
因为“真棒
would take up too much space."
会占用太多空间。”
And you guys give me shit
for a tiny gold chain?
你们给我大便
I regret nothing. I'm
going to get coffee.
我后悔没有。我
Hey, Brownie, you coming?
嘿，布朗尼，你来吗？
I was thinking we'd hit
the Philz on Middlefield.
我想我们会打
No, let's drive to the
one on Forest Avenue.
不，让我们开车去
It's further from that jacket.
它离那件夹克更进一步。
Claude, you're on pager
duty until we get back.
克劳德，你的传呼机
Jared, can I borrow that jacket?
贾里德，我能借那件夹克吗？
I sense you're doing
something ironic with it,
我感觉你正在做
but I'm okay with that because...
但我很好，因为…
however unattractive this
jacket may seem to you,
然而吸引力这
once you slip it on,
everything will change.
一旦你滑倒了，
It'll shake out its hair
and take off its glasses,
它会抖掉它的头发
and before you know it,
you'll be in love.
在你知道之前，
Jared, it's really fucking ugly.
贾里德，真他妈的丑。
Consider the tortoise.
考虑乌龟。
As the fable teaches us,
正如寓言教导我们，
it may appear that he
is losing in his race
可能会出现他
against his nemesis, the
insolent and cocksure hare.
对他的对手的
But appearances can be deceiving.
但外表可以欺骗。
Gavin, the tortoise. Is it Endframe?
加文，乌龟。这是端？
Yes. But there's more.
是的.但还有更多。
The hare is Pied Piper.
兔子是吹笛手。
Indeed it is. Someone's
read their Aesop.
事实上它是。某人的
We've also read the financials, Gavin.
我们也读金融，加文。
Between Nucleus and Endframe,
you've burned through
核和端之间，
three-quarters of a billion dollars,
十亿美元的四分之三，
with virtually nothing to show for it.
几乎没有什么可以显示它。
Two weeks ago, on the
heels of powering down
前2个星期，在
the entire Hooli campus
for seemingly no reason,
整个hooli校园
you lost all of Endframe's
senior engineers.
你失去了所有的端
I grant you, we've stumbled
on offense of late,
我给你，我们已经绊倒
but the best offense is a good defense.
但最好的进攻是一个很好的防守。
We've taken a page out
of Apple's playbook
我们已经采取了一页
and are currently "reviewing"
the Pied Piper app for sale
目前正在“审查”
in our Hooli store at a pace one
might call "tortoise-like."
在我们的hooli店的步伐，一
Don't. They hate that.
他们讨厌那。
In any case, I have it on good authority
在任何情况下，我都有良好的权威
that it may be some
time before Pied Piper
它可能是一些
is available on Hooli OS devices.
可在hooli OS设备。
- We're making it available immediately.
- Sorry?
•我们马上就可以了。
You're fighting a war that's already
ended, Gavin. Pied Piper won.
你已经在打一场战争
We called this board meeting to inform
you that it's time for Hooli to let go
我们打电话给董事会会议通知
and move on without you at the wheel.
没有你在车轮上前进。
I'm sorry, without me?
Are you firing me?
对不起，没有我？
Our intention is simply
to transition you
我们的意图很简单
into a more appropriate
role within the company,
进入一个更为合适的
one with less oversight
of day-to-day operations.
少了一个监督
You're putting me on the fucking roof?
你把我放在他妈的屋顶？
You could always choose to
move on, Gavin. Up to you.
你可以一直选择
I built this company with my
bare hands in my fucking garage.
我用我的
Where were you when I was doing that?
我在干什么的时候你在哪里？
Gavin?
加文？
These animals?
这些动物吗？
Fuck.
他妈的。
Well, uh, you are certainly more than
qualified to be our new head of PR.
嗯，你肯定比
Laurie thinks you're great. Um, to
be honest, we could use the help.
劳丽认为你是伟大的。嗯，到
All the media stuff has been pretty
overwhelming, especially lately.
所有媒体的东西都很漂亮
- If Marissa Mayer can do it, so can you.
- Oh.
如果玛丽莎Mayer能做到，那么你可以。
And, uh, you're available immediately?
嗯，你马上就可以了？
I am. I do have one
question for you guys.
我是.我有一个
Is everything here... cool?
这里的一切…酷吗？
Is it cool? Uh, yeah.
很酷吗？嗯，是的。
Yeah, I mean, I'm-- I'm cool.
是的，我是说，我很酷。
- Yeah, he is cool.
- Uh-huh.
是的，他很酷。
Clearly, but is there
anything you guys want
显然，但在那里
to tell me... about the company?
告诉我…关于公司？
What, like, uh--
什么，像，嗯-
All right, look, this is weird,
好吧，看，这很奇怪，
but when I was in Laurie's
office yesterday,
但当我在劳丽的
I saw a piece of paper on her desk.
我在她的桌子上看到一张纸。
Well, she--
she can be a bit untidy.
好吧，她--
It was a sale of a big
block of Pied Piper stock.
这是一个大的销售
Is someone on the inside
是某人在里面
dumping shares right
as you're launching?
倾销股票的权利
What?
什么？
No. No, absolutely not.
不，绝对不。
'Cause that would be a pretty
severe signaling risk.
这将是一个美丽的原因
I mean, you don't have to be
in PR to know that insiders
我是说，你不必
only dump stock like that when
they know something is wrong.
只有转储股票，当
The bulk of my compensation
here would be options,
我的大部分补偿
and if those aren't going
to be worth anything--
如果那些不去
Yeah. No. No, no, no.
是 啊.不，不，不，不
That is not happening, okay?
Nothing is going on here.
那不是发生，好吗？
- Yeah, except excellence.
- Okay.
-是的，除了卓越。
Well, you let me know
what you want to do
好吧，你让我知道
and I'll think about it.
我会考虑一下。
Okay. Oh.
可以.哦.
Um, well, thanks for coming.
嗯，谢谢你的到来。
What the hell was that?
那是什么？
Maybe it was a negotiating tactic?
也许这是一个谈判策略？
Monica.
莫妮卡。
It's Monica.
我是摩妮卡。
Well, let's not jump to conclusions.
好吧，让我们不要跳转到结论。
I mean, she's the only one
who's bought a jacket.
我是说，她是唯一一个
Jared, she's the only one
who hates the platform.
贾里德，她是唯一一个
There's no other explanation for this.
Okay? Monica fucked us.
对此没有其他解释。
She pulled down her pants and
fucked us in front of her parents.
她把裤子拉下来
Did some-- Richard, did
somebody do that to you?
做了一些-李察，没有
No. No, I don't know why--
不，不，我不知道为什么
Oh, boy, it is chilly.
哦，男孩，这是寒冷的。
Good thing I brought
this sweet jiz-acket.
我带来的好东西
Eh, friend? We came here together.
嗯，朋友？我们一起来到这里。
I know what you're doing.
我知道你在做什么。
You think you're embarrassing me,
你认为你让我难堪，
but that's only the secondary
effect of that shitty jacket.
但这只是次要的
The primary effect is...
主要作用是…
that you
look like a douchebag.
你
Let me put this in terms
you'll understand.
让我把这个放在
I'm like a suicide
bomber of humiliation.
我像一个自杀
I'm happy to go out as long
as I take you with me.
我很高兴能出去
Your shame is my paradise.
你的耻辱是我的天堂。
S'up, ladies?
s'up，女士们？
What you noshing on? Cranberry scone?
你喜欢吗？蔓越莓英式松饼？
My friend Dinesh here has a
little crush on you. He's shy.
我的朋友就在这里了
I don't know him.
我不认识他。
Oh, he plays coy.
哦，他是腼腆的。
I don't know why he's so shy.
我不知道他为什么这么害羞。
Excuse me. I noticed your jacket.
请原谅我。我注意到你的夹克。
Do you work for Pied Piper?
你吹笛手的工作吗？
- Yeah.
- Dude, your app is killin' it.
-是的。
Everyone I know is installing it.
我所认识的每个人都在安装。
Do you seriously? I just
downloaded it last night.
你真的很认真吗？我只是
Yeah? Do you mind if we get a picture?
是吗？你不介意我们有一张照片吗？
- With me?
- Yeah. Everybody get in.
和我在一起？
If you want it.
如果你想要它。
- Thanks.
- Thanks, bro.
-谢谢。
Hey, man, did you remember
to put money in the meter?
嘿，伙计，你还记得吗
Hi, I'm Dinesh. I work at Pied Piper.
嗨，我就。我在吹笛手的工作。
Excuse me, do I know you?
对不起，我认识你吗？
Gilfoyle.
吉尔福伊尔。
He's a fuckin' dick, but
I love him, though.
他是个该死的家伙，但是
You have me confused with someone else.
你让我与别人混淆。
My name's clearly Jared, and if you
would excuse us, you were interrupting.
我的名字是贾里德，如果你
No, he's lying. His name is Gilfoyle.
Show them your driver's license.
不，他在撒谎。他的名字是吉尔福伊尔。
Jared asked you nicely to step back,
贾里德很好地让你退一步，
so step the fuck back. You're being
a dick, and you're cutting in line.
所以他妈的背。你被
You heard him. You're being a dick.
你听到他。你是一个迪克。
- Boy, some people.
- What a creep.
•男孩，有些人。
Sorry you had to
deal with that, Jared.
对不起你不得不
You and me both, friend.
你和我都是朋友。
This is Monica.
这是莫妮卡。
Is it? Because apparently
everything else
是吗？因为很显然，
that comes out of your mouth is a lie.
从你的嘴里出来是一个谎言。
Shit.
倒霉.
Look, Richard, I totally
understand if you're pissed at me,
听着，李察，我完全
but please know that I tried as hard
as I could to get him to tell you.
但请知道，我尽了努力
Oh, really? Well, that's
not what he said.
哦，真的吗？嗯，那是
Oh, really? What exactly did he say?
哦，真的吗？他究竟说了什么？
He said that he found it on a piece
of paper in Laurie's office.
他说他在一块
What? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Who's
the "he" that you're talking about?
什么？等待，等待，等待。坚持。是谁
You know who. David.
你知道谁。戴维。
- My brother?
- What?
我弟弟？
Who the fuck-- I don't know.
他妈的--我不知道。
No, David, the fucking PR guy
不，戴维，那个他妈的
who's not going to take a job
with us because of what you did.
谁不打算找工作
Richard, I am totally lost. What
exactly do you think I did?
李察，我完全迷路了。什么
You can play dumb all you want to.
It won't change the one thing
你可以扮演哑你想。
that both you and I know is true.
You dumped your stock.
你和我都知道这是真的。
What? No. I didn't dump a single
share of my Pied Piper stock.
什么？不。我没有转储一个单一的
I swear. Well, then who the fuck did?
我发誓。那么，谁他妈的呢？
And make sure that the money reads.
并确保钱读。
I mean, Pied Piper is a
billion-dollar company.
我的意思是，吹笛人是一个
It's not just a unicorn.
这不只是独角兽。
All right, let's do some rearing.
好吧，让我们做一些饲养。
There we go. Now, let's let the horns
我们去那里。现在让我们让角
sort of look like my dick. Perfect.
像我的迪克排序。很 完美.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Richard.
-你他妈的跟我开玩笑吧？
Um, can we take a soft five?
嗯，我们能不能软五？
I was going to tell you. That's
what tomorrow's brunch was for.
我要告诉你。这是
Brunch? You had ten fucking days
and you didn't say a thing.
早午餐？你有十个他妈的天
Fine. You want to know
why I didn't tell you?
好的.你想知道
Because it's fucking humiliating.
I'm broke, Richard.
因为这是他妈的耻辱。
Did you hear me? I'm broke.
你听到我了吗？我打破了。
Erlich Bachman, the name that used
to be synonymous with success,
法国巴赫曼，使用的名称
went broke and was forced to sell.
又被强行推销。
- I got royally fucked, Richard.
- You got fucked?
-我有非常糟糕，李察。
You're the one who threw
a million-dollar party.
你是那个扔的人
- Yeah, but it was a great party.
- No one forced you to do that.
-是的，但它是一个伟大的党。
Admit it, you fucked yourself.
承认吧，你和你自己。
But I'm not gonna let
you fuck my company.
但我不会让
I'm going to have to
issue a press release
我要去
explaining what you did and why.
解释你做了什么，为什么。
No, no, come on. This isn't out.
不，不，来。这不是出来。
- It's one PR guy.
- That we know of, Erlich.
•这是一个公关人员。
How many other people saw
that piece of paper?
有多少人看到
How many people has this guy talked to?
这家伙跟他说了多少人？
This is Silicon Valley.
这是硅谷。
Rumors spread like light speed here.
谣言如光在这里传播。
How are we gonna get good
people to work for us
我们怎么会得到好
if they think something funky
is going on with our stock?
如果他们觉得时髦
How are we going to scale?
This is going to kill us.
我们将如何规模？
Richard, do you know what
happens if this goes public?
李察，你知道吗
- I'm Ron Wayne.
- Who?
•我是韦恩。
Ron Wayne. The guy that owned ten
percent of Apple and sold it in 1976.
罗恩韦恩。那个人拥有十
No one in this town will
work with me ever again.
这镇上没有人会
You want me to risk the
entire future of Pied Piper,
你要我冒风险
everything that I've worked for,
我工作的一切，
just to protect you from your
own fucking incompetence?
只是为了保护你不受你的
Richard, there's a three
to four percent chance
李察，有一三
that this is going to
get out on its own,
这是要
but there is 100 percent chance
但有百分之100个机会
that if you issue a press release
如果你发行了新闻稿
no one will ever take
me seriously again.
永远没有人能接受
My dignity is in your hands, Richard.
我的尊严是在你的手中，李察。
Do with it what you will.
做你将做的。
Gavin? Is that you?
加文？是你吗？
- Jack Barker.
- Nice plane.
杰克-巴克。
- Yours too.
- Where are you headed?
•你的。
I just needed to take a
walk and clear my head.
我只需要带一个
There's this great little hiking
trail near my lodge in Jackson Hole.
这个伟大的小远足
Get out of here. I'm on my
way up to J Hole myself.
离开这里。我在我的
Is that right? I thought you sold.
是不是？我以为你卖了。
No, I just never go there.
不，我只是不去那里。
So how long you going for?
你要去多久？
Coming back tomorrow afternoon.
明天下午回来。
- Me, too.
- Oh, come on. Come on.
我也。
Seriously, we need to find a couple
hours, get together, catch up.
说真的，我们需要找到一对夫妇
I could tell you some war stories.
我可以告诉你一些战争故事。
Well, I'd love that.
哦，我很喜欢。
I could tell you a few of my own.
我可以告诉你我自己的一些。
Well, be well.
嗯，很好。
- You, too.
- Take care, Jack.
-你，太。
- Yeah.
- See you.
-是的。
Gavin? Wait.
加文？等待.
Uh, what are we doing here?
嗯，我们在这里干什么？
I mean, you're on your way to Jackson
Hole, I'm going to Jackson Hole.
我是说，你在去禅师的路上
You seem like you could
use some company.
你似乎能
- You play chess?
- I do. Indeed.
你下象棋？
Fantastic. I tell you,
when we get up to altitude
好极了.我告诉你，
and the Wi-Fi kicks in, I'm
ActionJB62 on Hooli chat.
和Wi-Fi踢，我是
- Find me.
- I will.
找到我。
- I'm glad we bumped into each other.
- Me, too.
•我很高兴我们撞到了彼此。
- Really is a small world.
- It's crazy.
真是一个小世界。
Okay, well, uh, I think it reads well.
好吧，呃，我想这读起来很好。
And it's all in there. This will
definitely set the record straight.
这都是在那里。这将
Then again, you're basically
lighting Erlich on fire.
然后，你基本上是
So what? He fucked the company.
还等什么？他把公司。
He potentially fucked the company.
他可能把公司。
Are you kidding me? Wh--
Gilfoyle, back me up here.
你在跟我开玩笑吧？那--
This is thorny.
这是棘手的。
How is this even a
question for you guys?
这是怎样的一个
Honestly? I mean, it's
not like he's going
真的吗？我的意思是，它是
to be out on the street.
He just sold ten percent
在街上。
of a company that's valued at
at least 50 million dollars
一个被估价的公司
and now suddenly we're giving
him the benefit of the doubt?
现在突然我们给
Well, it sounds mighty
Christian of you, Gilfoyle.
听起来很强大
There's no reason for
hate speech, Richard.
没有理由的
I can see by the sour,
pinched expressions
我可以看到的酸，
on all your faces that
Richard has filled you in
在你所有的脸上
regarding the unfortunate
circumstances that have forced me
对于不幸的
to relinquish my stake
in your fair company.
放弃我的股份
Erlich, uh, you should know that
I have written a press release.
埃利希，呃，你应该知道
- Oh?
- I'm not going to release it yet,
-哦？
but if I hear wind of these rumors
但如果我听到这些谣言的风声
spreading out of control, I'm going
to send it to every tech publication
传播失控，我要去
and blog on the face of the earth.
Do you understand?
和博客的脸上的地球。
- Even UPROXX?
- Yes, even them.
即使Uproxx？
Also, uh...
还有，嗯…
this is the check for next month's
use of the house as our office,
这是下个月的检查
but we'll be out by
the end of the month.
但我们会被
Richard, it doesn't
have to be like this.
李察，它不
From this point forward,
you will have nothing
从这一点向前，
to do with this company whatsoever.
与这家公司做任何。
I'm replacing you on the board,
我在董事会上取代你，
and I'm giving your seat to Jared.
我给你的座位给贾里德。
- So that's it then.
- Yes.
-所以这是它。
So I guess we better get ready
for that "Vanity Fair" event.
所以我想我们最好做好准备
What?
什么？
Did you not listen to
a word I just said?
你没有听
I heard thousands of words about rumors
我听到了关于谣言的数千个词
and the need to contain them.
What do you think would happen
和需要包含它们。
if I didn't show up to
this "Vanity Fair" event?
如果我没有出现
I've already RSVP'd
and given them a list
我已经回复过
of phony dietary restrictions
just to cause a scene.
虚假的饮食限制
I told them I was pesca-pescatarian.
我告诉他们我是帕斯卡pescatarian。
Which is one who eats solely
fish who eat other fish.
这是一个谁吃完全
I think my absence would be noted.
我想我的缺席会被注意到。
- Erlich brings up a good point.
- It's true.
•埃利希带来了一个好点的。
Let us not forget
Meinertzhagen's Havers--
让我们不要忘记
Yes, yes, Meinertzhagen's Haversack.
是的，是的，梅纳茨哈根的背包。
We all remember his sack.
我们都记得他的袋子。
Okay, fine. Yeah.
好的，好的。是 啊.
Sure. You can come. I can't stop you.
当然.你可以来。我不能阻止你。
Uh, I'll be taking the
car and the hotel room
嗯，我要带了
and you're going to
have to drive yourself.
你要去
Consider it my farewell dinner.
认为这是我的告别晚宴。
See you at the event.
看到你在活动。
- Jared, are you okay?
- It's just so many emotions.
-贾里德，你还好吗？
The board seat. I feel regret and glee
董事会席位。我感到遗憾和欢乐
that you would choose to honor me,
你会选择为我荣耀，
and terror at not living up
和恐怖在不住
to your expectations,
对你的期望，
and compassion for Erlich's loss.
和法国的损失的同情。
Oh, Donald, you've come undone.
哦，唐纳德，你来了。
You still want him on the board?
你还是要他在船上？
Hi, there. Checking in.
Richard Hendricks.
嗨，有。检查。
Fuck me. Hey, Richie.
他妈的我。嘿，里奇。
Oh, God. Hey, Russ.
哦，上帝。嘿，罗斯。
What's up, boy genius? You here fucking?
什么了，男孩天才？你他妈的？
Huh? No. No, no, no fucking.
嗯？不，不，不，他妈的。
Just, uh, here for the
"Vanity Fair" dinner.
只是，嗯，在这里
Oh, yeah, I know that stupid dinner.
哦，是的，我知道那个愚蠢的晚餐。
Bunch of VC douchebags
jerking each other off.
VC资源束
Speaking of, I got this girl at
the bar, I'm trying to take her
说到，我得到了这个女孩
up to the presidential suite
before her fucking bridesmaids
到总统套房
ruin the whole thing, but
they're telling me it's booked.
毁掉整个事情，但
Who is it? Is it Gore? Fuck that guy.
是谁？这是戈尔？去他妈的。
- Oh, God.
- I saw Pied Piper launched.
-哦，上帝。
Haven't tried it, probably won't.
没有尝试过，可能不会。
I don't even want to think
about how fucked I got
我甚至不想思考
missing out on Erlich's shares. Fuck.
错过了法国的股票。他妈的。
Wait, he-- he tried to
sell you his shares?
等等，他试着去
Well, half of them. He was pretty
desperate to stay on the team.
好，一半。他是漂亮的
Well, he didn't mention
anything about this to me.
他没有提到
Of course not. Why would he? It's fucking
humiliating losing all your money.
当然不是。他为什么会？这是他妈的
You think when I dropped below a billion
I walked around telling everybody?
你认为当我下降到十亿以下
Fuck no. You guys were
the only ones who knew,
他妈的没有
and I actually thought
about having you killed.
我真的想
- I'm sorry, what?
- So Erlich and I, like two weeks ago,
-我很抱歉，是什么？
we had a contract ready... five mil I
was gonna pay him for half his shares.
我们有合同准备好了…五密我
It was a win-win. Then
that robot, Laurie Bream,
这是一个双赢。然后
sweeps in and cockblocks
the whole thing.
和cockblocks扫描
She forces him to sell her all
his shares. You think she's gay?
她强迫他把她所有的
Maybe. It hasn't come up. I,
uh-- so wait, she outbid you?
也许 吧.它还没有出现。我，
Outbid me? No, she didn't have to.
出价比我高吗？不，她没有。
You don't even know how your own
fucking company works?
你甚至不知道你自己的
All right, Mr. Hendricks, we
have you staying one night
好的，先生。亨德里克斯，我们
- in a deluxe double.
- Okay, do you have a tub in that room?
在一个豪华的双。
Does he have a tub in that room?
他在那个房间里有一个浴缸吗？
I don't know. There's no way of telling.
我不知道。没有办法告诉。
You know what? Fuck it. I'm
gonna take her to the "W."
你知道吗？去他妈的。我
She's so drunk she won't know the
difference. See you around, Richie.
她这么醉，她不知道
Hey, it's CJ.
Listen, I'm hearing a rumor
嘿，这是CJ。
about some serious ugliness
going on at Pied Piper.
关于一些严重的丑陋
I've heard it from three different
people now. You need to call me.
我从三个不同的
Fuck.
他妈的。
What in God's name is the
reason to get a higher education?
上帝的名字是什么
You can just buy a
megafreeze for 35 cents.
你只能买一个
Laurie, can I talk to you for a second?
劳丽，我能跟你谈谈吗？
Yes, uh, Richard Hendricks,
是的，呃，李察亨德里克斯，
- do you know Mark Pincus?
- Hello.
你知道Mark Pincus？
- Big fan.
- Oh, okay. Yes.
•大风扇。
- Sorry, just one second.
- Yes. Oh, all right.
-对不起，只有一秒。
I'm sorry to cut away like this.
We can continue discussing this.
我很抱歉这样就把这个。
Okay, uh, look,
好吧，嗯，看，
I know Erlich sold you
all of his shares.
我知道法国卖给你
I'm just, uh, wondering
exactly how that happened.
我只是，嗯，想知道
Ah, yes. It was one of my finer moments.
啊，是的。这是我美好的时刻之一。
Erlich came to me with an outside offer
to sell half of his Pied Piper shares.
埃利希来到我与外界提供
To Russ Hanneman for five
million dollars. Yes, I know.
罗斯Hanneman五
But somehow you ended up
with all of his shares. How?
但不知怎的你结束了
Oh, well, as you know, the same
onerous terms you accepted
哦，好吧，正如你所知道的一样
when you took Russ Hanneman's money,
当你把罗斯Hanneman的钱，
they transferred to me
when I bought him out.
他们转移到我
These included the right to
block any transfer of stocks
这些包括权利
with a majority vote of the board.
A board which I control.
与董事会的多数票。
- I don't understand.
- Of course you do.
•我不明白。
If I have approval of any buyer,
如果我得到任何买家的认可，
and I am the only buyer I approve,
我是唯一的买家，我同意，
then I can set my own price.
然后我可以设置我自己的价格。
So I asked Mr. Bachman for a thorough
accounting of his debts, uh,
所以我请巴赫曼先生作一个彻底的
which ran to approximately $713,000.
其中跑了约713000美元。
And how much did you give him?
你给他多少钱？
$713,000.
713000美元。
Jesus. So, he walked away with nothing.
耶稣。于是，他什么也没有走了。
Uh, yes. And so as I said,
嗯，是的。所以我说，
you're the one who accepted these terms,
你是接受这些条款的人，
so you're the one who enabled
this action on my part.
所以你是一个启用
All credit goes to you, Richard.
Excuse me.
所有的荣誉都归功于你，李察。
Dick. Dick Costolo. One moment.
迪克。Dick Costolo。那一刻。
I need to speak with you.
我需要和你说话。
It's expensive to re-plant.
这是昂贵的重新工厂。
No. The vines are bad. The soil is bad.
不，葡萄树坏了。土壤不好。
Excuse me, what is that?
对不起，那是什么？
That's pesca-pescatarian.
这是帕斯卡pescatarian。
- It's fish that--
- Actually, just bring me one of those.
-这是鱼
- Me, too.
- Yeah, waiter, I'll take on, too.
我也。
- I want one.
- I want one of those also.
•我想要一个。
Wait, hey, hey,
I'd like that also.
等等，嘿，嘿，
Excuse me, if he's
having one, I want one.
原谅我，如果他是
You're getting that,
I want it, too. Excuse me!
你得到了，
Hey, I thought you were at the dinner.
嘿，我以为你在吃晚饭。
I left.
我离开。
Erlich never showed. Is he here?
埃利希从未出现。他在这儿吗？
Yeah. He's hiding in the backyard.
是 啊.他躲在后院里。
- Why?
- Have you not seen the article?
-为什么？
No.
不.
"Is Erlich Bachman the
Dumbest Man in Tech?"
“法国巴赫曼
What the hell is this? I
never sent anything out.
这到底是什么？我
- Who did they talk to?
- Erlich.
他们和谁说话了？
This is CJ's blog. He outed
himself to protect Pied Piper.
这是CJ的博客。他了
This is way harsher than
anything you ever wrote.
这是更严厉的比
Plus, there's the visual component.
此外，还有视觉组件。
Speaking of... where's
your jacket, Jared?
说起…在哪里
That's quite a piece.
那是相当的一块。
Informative. Thorough.
见闻。彻底的。
You certainly know how
to make an impact.
你当然知道
And I guess I don't have to worry
about any rumors coming out.
我想我不必担心
Those are handled.
这些都是处理。
You know, Erlich, uh, Pied Piper
still needs a head of PR.
你知道，埃利希，呃，吹笛手
You seem to be well-versed
in media outreach.
你似乎很精通
And by your own admission
in that article,
并通过你自己的录取
your head is--
what did you say?
你的头
--so far up your own ass
you can see the future.
-那么你自己的屁股
And that could be useful...
这可能是有用的…
if we need a pre-cog...
如果我们需要一个预齿轮…
in a way?
以一种方式？
Uh, I don't know if
you're available, so...
嗯，我不知道
Are you offering me a job?
你给我提供一份工作吗？
Well, we have a good option package.
好了，我们有一个好的选择包。
Um, it won't be quite what
you had, but it's something.
嗯，这不会是什么
That's very generous.
那是非常慷慨的。
So things could go back to
the way they were before.
所以事情可以回到过去
Well, no. No. Not exactly
the way they were.
不，不完全
No, no. Uh, well, this
would be an actual job
不，不，嗯，这
and you would have responsibilities.
你会有责任。
Would this job have a title?
这项工作有一个标题吗？
Something, say, Chief
Evangelism Officer?
总有一些话，说
So, CEO?
那么，首席执行官？
- Oh, my goodness!
- What the fuck was that?
哦，我的天！
Richard.
李察。
The Pied Piper app just got
accepted to the Hooli store.
吹笛的应用刚
What? Holy shit.
什么？天啊.
Gavin Belson just presented us with
his bare buttocks in submission.
加文贝尔森只是我们
We beat him. I
don't-- I don't hug. No.
我们打败了他。我
Um, okay, hey, look, uh, time to issue
your first press release, right?
嗯，好吧，嘿，看，嗯，时间到了
It's very late, Richard,
and I'm very high.
很晚了，李察，
Erlich, I don't care.
艾，我不在乎。
You have to do it, okay? Now.
你必须这样做，好吗？现在.
- It's your job.
- Okay.
•这是你的工作。
- All right.
- Oh!
•所有权利。
CJ Cantwell. Erlich Bachman.
CJ坎特。法国巴赫曼。
The reason I'm calling has
absolutely nothing to do
我打电话的原因
whatsoever with the fact
that I own half of your blog
与事实有什么
and everything to do with the fact that
和所有的事情，这样做的事实
I was just named Chief Evangelism
Officer of Pied Piper.
我刚刚被任命为首席布道
Feel free to abbreviate that,
whatever acronym is most economical.
随意缩写，
And I have a story.
我有一个故事。
Well, if it's anything like
this last one, I am all for it.
好吧，如果它是什么
I am getting so many paid
views on your tell-all.
我得到这么多的报酬
Everyone in the Valley is reading it.
山谷里的每个人都在看它。
Well, that's good... for you...
好了，好了…为你...
at my expense, I guess.
以我的费用，我想。
Anyway, I had no choice.
无论如何，我别无选择。
As you said, it was going to
come out one way or another.
正如你所说的，这将是
Why? No one knew about any
of it until you told me.
为什么？谁也不知道
What do you mean? You said that you
had heard from a bunch of people
你是什么意思？你说你
that there are all these rumors about
ugly shit going down at Pied Piper.
有所有这些谣言
That's literally the only reason
that I told you any of this.
这是真正的唯一原因
What? Oh, yeah, three
different people told me
什么？哦，是的，三
that Pied Piper had the ugliest
jackets they'd ever seen.
那吹笛人有丑
Jackets?
夹克？
I was going to do, like, a whole
swag fail thing, you know.
我要做的，像，一个整体
That could have been cool, no?
那会很酷，不是吗？
Who the fuck cares about jackets?
谁他妈的关心夹克？
♪ Hey, come on, babe ♪
♪嘿，来吧，宝贝♪
♪ Follow me ♪
♪跟着我♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper ♪
♪我吹笛♪
♪ Follow me, I'm the Pied Piper ♪
♪跟着我，我吹笛♪
♪ And I'll show you where it's at ♪
♪我会告诉你它在哪♪
♪ Come on, babe can't you see? ♪
♪来吧，宝贝，难道你看不出来吗？♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper, trust in me ♪
♪我吹笛，信任我♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper ♪
♪我吹笛♪
♪ And I'll show you where it's at ♪
♪我会告诉你它在哪♪
♪ Girl, don't be scared to move ♪
♪女孩，不要害怕移动♪
♪ Hey, babe, what are
you tryin' to prove? ♪
♪嘿，宝贝，是什么
♪ It ain't true that your
life has kicked you ♪
♪这不是真实的你
♪ It's your mind and that's
all that's trickin' you ♪
♪这是你的心，
♪ So step in line ♪
♪所以线♪步
♪ Hey, come on, babe, follow me ♪
♪嘿，来吧，宝贝，跟我♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper, follow me ♪
♪我吹笛，跟着我♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper ♪
♪我吹笛♪
♪ And I'll show you where it's at ♪
♪我会告诉你它在哪♪
♪ Come on, babe, can't you see? ♪
♪来吧，宝贝，难道你看不出来吗？♪
♪ Come on, babe, follow me ♪
♪来吧，宝贝，跟我♪
♪ I'm the Pied Piper ♪
♪我吹笛♪